{
    "lvl4" :[
        {
            "question":"Which of the following is NOT a primitive data type: int, boolean,float, double, Array" ,
            "answer": "Array",
            "id" :1
        },
        {
            "question":"What is the range of data type 'short' in Java: A: -2344556, B: -32768:32767, C:-128:127, D: None of the above",   
            "answer": "-32768:32767",
            "id" :2
        },
        {
            "question":"What is the range of data type 'byte' in Java: A: -2499399:2499400, B: -128:127, C: -32768:32767, D: None of the above" ,
            "answer": "-128:127",
            "id" :3
        },
        {
            "question":"An expression involving byte, int, and literal numbers is promoted to which of these: A: int, B: long, C: float, D: boolean" ,
            "answer": "int",
            "id" :4
        },
        {
            "question": "Which data type value is returned by all transcendental math functions" ,
            "answer": "double",
            "id" :5
        },
        {
            "question":"What is the size(bytes) of the data type 'float' in Java?" ,
            "answer": "4",
            "id" :6
        },
        {
            "question":"What is the size(bytes) of the data type 'double' in Java?" ,
            "answer": "8",
            "id" :7
        },
        {
            "question":"What is the size(bytes) of the data type 'char' in Java?" ,
            "answer": "2",
            "id" :8
        },
        {
            "question":"What is the size(bytes) of the data type 'int' in Java?" ,
            "answer": "4",
            "id" :9
        },
        {
            "question":"The following number is an example of what primitive data type: 254.4f ?" ,
            "answer": "float",
            "id" :10
        }
    ]
}